colibritool.com 2018-08-20

# Airtweets - Privacy

  1. **Privacy policy  
** This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which ColibriTool Sp. z o.o. collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the https://airtweets.com website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by ColibriTool Sp. z o.o..

 **Personal identification information  
**  
We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, place an order, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, credit card information. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

 **Non-personal identification information  
**  
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

 **Web browser cookies  
**  
Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

 **How we use collected information  
**  
ColibriTool Sp. z o.o. may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:  
\- To improve customer service. Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.  
\- To personalize user experience. We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.  
\- To improve our Site. We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.  
\- To process payments. We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.  
\- To send periodic emails. We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

 **How we protect your information  
**  
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.

 **Sharing your personal information  
**  
Submitted Information. When registering for an account on Airtweets, we will collect the following information: (i) your e-mail address and (ii) a unique password. 

When paying to use the Site, we may collect information from you including: name and surname or company name, evidential numbers (tax identity number, registration number in relevant court, administrative or commercial registers - in case of corporate entities), billing address and credit card information. If you submit payment information, we do not store credit card numbers you may use to make payments on the Site. Payment information is passed on to our third-party payment processors, PayPal Inc. and PayLane Sp. z o.o. (80-387 Gdańsku ul. Arkonska 6/A3, KRS: 0000227278), which handle payments and refunds for us. For information on PayPal’s privacy practices, you can review their privacy policy at https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full. For information on PayLane’s privacy practices, you can review their privacy policy at http://palane.com/privacy-policy. 

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.

 **Compliance with children's online privacy protection act  
**  
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our Site from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

 **Changes to this privacy policy  
**  
ColibriTool Sp. z o.o. has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

 **Your acceptance of these terms  
**  
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

 **Contacting us  
**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:

ColibriTool Sp. z o.o.  
https://airtweets.com  
Mokotowska 1  
00-640 Warszawa  
hi@airtweets.com

This document was last updated on March 5th, 2015
